#### **Edwin Adrián Cosme Nolasco**

Playa del Carmen, México · adriancosme15@gmail.com · (+52) 984 153 69 59 · <u>edwincosme.vercel.app</u> · <u>linkedin.com/in/edwin-cosme</u> · <u>github.com/adriancosme</u>

+2 years of experience as software engineer working primarily with the JavaScript tech stack, including Nestjs, Express, React, and Vue. Proficient in developing efficient applications. Known for being a fast learner, team player, and always seeking opportunities to provide assistance and contribute to the growth and success of the company and teams.

### **Experience**

31Rooms [Consulting] Remote

**Full-stack Developer** 

November 2021 – January 2023 (1 year, 3 months)

- Optimized e-commerce product search response times by 90% through successful implementation of Elasticsearch.
- Improved ETL scripts for synchronizing product databases, reducing processing time by 90% from 5 hours to just 30 minutes.
- Created and implemented a custom chat module on AWS utilizing AWS Lambda and API Gateway technologies.
- Implemented CI/CD pipelines using GitHub Actions, resulting in significantly reduced deployment time for applications.
- Developed a chat-based queue system for handling incoming inquiries, facilitating efficient and organized customer support.
- Built websites for external companies using Javascript technologies such as Nodejs, Nestjs, React, Vue.

# Meguz Telecom [Consulting, SaaS]

Playa del Carmen, Quintana Roo

Full-stack Developer

October 2020 – October 2021 (1 year)

- Played a key role in the development of a highly efficient real-time delivery system, contributing to the
  design, implementation, and testing phases, resulting in a successful and reliable system that significantly
  improved delivery times and customer satisfaction.
- Migrated a point-of-sale (POS) system from Vue.js single-page application (SPA) to Nuxt.js server-side rendering (SSR), resulting in improved performance and removing tech debt from source code.
- Designed and developed a billing module for a school administration system to improve tracking and efficiently charge for enrollment and tuition fees, resulting in enhanced financial management.
- Maintained an internal package that generated a CFDI(Comprobante Fiscal Digital por Internet) in XML and PDF format for billing systems in compliance with government regulations.
- Implemented new features into the internal billing system, ensuring its optimal performance and uninterrupted operation.

#### Skills

- Javascript, Typescript, Python, PHP
- NodeJs, Express, Nestjs
- React Native
- Azure, AWS, DigitalOcean
- React, Next.js, Vue, Nuxt.js
- MySQL, PostgreSQL, MongoDB
- Docker

Certifications

SCRUMstudy
Azure Fundamentals (AZ-900)
Microsoft

Issue date: Jul. 2022

Issue date: Aug. 2022

### **Education**

Universidad Tecnológica de la Riviera Maya Engineer's degree in Information and Technology September 2017 - April 2021 Playa del Carmen, Quintana Roo

## Languages

- Spanish Native
- English B1